642weather.com 2009-06-21

# Privacy Policy for Long Beach Weather

### Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for[www.642weather.com](http://www.642weather.com/)**

Thank you for using Long Beach Weather ("LBW"). This page states the terms and conditions under which you may use the Web Site. Please read this page carefully. By accessing this Web Site you accept and agree to be bound, without limitation or qualification, by these Terms. If you do not accept any of the Terms stated here, do not use these Web Sites. LBW may, in its sole discretion, modify or revise the Terms at any time by updating this web page. You are bound by any such modification or revision and should therefore visit this page periodically to review the Terms. 

Long Beach Weather is committed to providing a secure environment at this web site. We are committed to protecting your personal information, leaving you free to express yourself with your friends and family. The following is our policy regarding access to your information. Please review it. We reserve the right to periodically update the policy, so you should periodically come back and review this page. 

**Personal Information**

When you choose to register an account, or make a donation, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, address, city, country, zip code and phone number. 

What do we do with this information?  
We use the name and email address to send you information and updates, and to provide you with correspondence when necessary. We use this information to verify registration and/or product offerings. We use some of the optional information to help us provide statistics to guide LBW (i.e. who is visiting us and from where) so that we can better reach people and invite them to the use this web site. 

What do we not do with the information?  
We don't sell your identity to any third parties. We don't sell your information you place on our sites to any third parties. 

**Cookies and IP Addresses**

There is additional information that can be gathered by an operating web site. One is the IP address (random numbers assigned to individual computers) of the machine you use to reach these sites. This information is used to help diagnose problems with our web site. Your IP address may also be used to block your access to areas of the site if we determine that you are abusing the sites resources. 

Another way to gather information is to use a cookie (small text file transferred from our Web Site to your hard drive). Our web site uses cookies to determine if you are logged in and also to save your login information to speed up your access to the sites. Cookies do not damage files or allow anyone to access your personally identifiable information - they simply allow us to tailor information and advertisements to make your visits more enjoyable and meaningful. They also provide information to us about site usage to help us improve and update our site. We may share aggregate (not individual) site usage statistics and demographic information with advertisers and other third parties, but this information will not include any personally identifiable information and this practice is not currently undertaken. 

**Privacy**

You acknowledge that all Communities are public and not private communications, and that therefore others may read your communications without your knowledge. Always use caution when giving out any personally identifying information about yourself or your family in any Community. LBW does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Community and, therefore, LBW specifically disclaims any liability with regard to the Communities and any actions resulting from your participation in any Community. Generally, any communication which you post to this Web Site (whether in chat rooms, discussion groups, message boards or otherwise) is considered to be non-confidential. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Web Site contain links to third party web sites that are maintained by others. These links are provided solely as a convenience to you and not as an endorsement by LBW of the contents on such third-party Web sites. LBW is not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites and does not make any representations regarding the content or accuracy of materials on such third-party Web sites. If you decide to access linked third-party Web sites, you do so at your own risk. 

**Indemnity**

You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless LBW, its officers, owners, members and agents, from and against any claims, actions or demands, including without limitation reasonable legal and accounting fees, alleging or resulting from your use of the Material (including Software) or your breach of the terms of this Agreement. LBW shall provide notice to you promptly of any such claim, suit, or proceeding and shall reasonably assist you, at your expense, in defending any such claim, suit or proceeding. 

**General**

LBW makes no claims that the Materials are appropriate for any particular purpose or audience, or that they may be downloaded outside of the United States. Access to the Materials (including Software) may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Web Site from outside of the United States, you are responsible for compliance with the laws of your jurisdiction. 

Comments that are sent to us about the web site may be quoted on the site, along with your location ie: Country, State or County but names, addresses and email addresses will never be published without permission. LBW will never share this information with any other person or web site for any purpose unless required to do so by law. 

LBW cannot be held responsible if personal information is leaked or accessed should the site be hacked. It is your responsibility to secure this data. 

**Additional Information**

Long Beach Weather reserves the right to alter our Privacy Policy as needs require. Any changes will be posted to our web site in a timely manner. This statement and the policies outlined here are not intended to and do not give you any contractual or other legal rights. 

If you have any questions, complaints or suggestions (remember, we did say to be nice) send us an email. We would love to hear from you. 

From the Long Beach Weather team, we thank you for using the site. Enjoy! 

Comments, questions or problems?  Contact Us

Webmaster last modified 29th May 2008
